{"test_questions": [[{"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Efficient", "optb": "Treatmeant", "optc": "Beterment", "optd": "Employd", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Foreign", "optb": "Foreine", "optc": "Fariegn", "optd": "Forein", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Ommineous", "optb": "Omineous", "optc": "Ominous", "optd": "Omenous", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Pessenger", "optb": "Passenger", "optc": "Pasanger", "optd": "Pesanger", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Benefitted", "optb": "Benifited", "optc": "Benefited", "optd": "Benefeted", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Treachrous", "optb": "Trecherous", "optc": "Trechearous", "optd": "Treacherous", "ans": "D", "explanation": "Treacherous means guilty of or involving betrayal or deception."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Forcast", "optb": "Forecaste", "optc": "Forcaust", "optd": "Forecast", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Rigerous", "optb": "Rigourous", "optc": "Regerous", "optd": "Rigorous", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Palete", "optb": "Palet", "optc": "Palate", "optd": "Pelate", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Bouquete", "optb": "Bouquette", "optc": "Bouquet", "optd": "Boqquet", "ans": "C", "explanation": "Bouquet - bunch of flowers, nosegay, fragrance of a wine, compliment."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Vetarinary", "optb": "Veteninary", "optc": "Vetinary", "optd": "Veterinary", "ans": "D", "explanation": "Veterinary  - pertaining to the medical treatment of animals"}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Chancelary", "optb": "Chancellery", "optc": "Chancelery", "optd": "Chancellary", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Excessive", "optb": "Exccessive", "optc": "Exxcesive", "optd": "Excesive", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Indipensable", "optb": "Indipenseble", "optc": "Indispansible", "optd": "Indispensable", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Humorous", "optb": "Ganerous", "optc": "Pupolous", "optd": "Maretorious", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Itinarery", "optb": "Itinerary", "optc": "Itenary", "optd": "Itinarary", "ans": "B", "explanation": "Itinerary - of a trip, of a journey, of travelling, of the route taken on a journey."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Survaillance", "optb": "Surveillance", "optc": "Survellance", "optd": "Surveilance", "ans": "B", "explanation": "Surveillance - careful observation of a person or group, supervision."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Sepulchral", "optb": "Sepilchrle", "optc": "Sepalchrul", "optd": "Sepalchrl", "ans": "A", "explanation": "Sepulchral - pertaining to a grave or tomb. (or) serving as a grave or tomb."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Acommodation", "optb": "Accomodaton", "optc": "Accommodation", "optd": "Acomodation", "ans": "C", "explanation": "Accommodation is used to refer to buildings or rooms where people live or stay."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Faithfuly", "optb": "Sincerely", "optc": "Truely", "optd": "Affectionatly", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Klaptomania", "optb": "Klepptomania", "optc": "Kleptemania", "optd": "Kleptomania", "ans": "D", "explanation": "Kleptomania: A recurrent urge to steal, typically without regard for need or profit."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Schedulle", "optb": "Schedeule", "optc": "Schdule", "optd": "Schedule", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Skillful", "optb": "Skillfull", "optc": "Skilfull", "optd": "Skilpull", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Judicious", "optb": "Cancious", "optc": "Dilicous", "optd": "Gracous", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Gaurantee", "optb": "Guarantee", "optc": "Garuntee", "optd": "Guaruntee", "ans": "B", "explanation": "Guarantee - vouch for, give a guarantee, give a warranty, promise, assure"}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Friming", "optb": "Burnning", "optc": "Running", "optd": "Fryng", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Dammage", "optb": "Damaige", "optc": "Dammege", "optd": "Damage", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Accomplish", "optb": "Acomplush", "optc": "Ackmplesh", "optd": "Accompalish", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Puerrile", "optb": "Puerrille", "optc": "Purrile", "optd": "Puerile", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Satelite", "optb": "Sattelite", "optc": "Satellite", "optd": "Sattellite", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Inoculation", "optb": "Innoculation", "optc": "Inocculation", "optd": "Inocullation", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Velnerable", "optb": "Vulnarable", "optc": "Vulnerable", "optd": "Valnerable", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Simpal", "optb": "Bannar", "optc": "Pattren", "optd": "Modern", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Scripher", "optb": "Scripture", "optc": "Skripture", "optd": "Scriptur", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Comitte", "optb": "Commitee", "optc": "Committee", "optd": "Comiittee", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Exaggerate", "optb": "Exeggrate", "optc": "Exagerate", "optd": "Exadgerate", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Asspersion", "optb": "Voluptuous", "optc": "Voguei", "optd": "Equestrain", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Hindrance", "optb": "Hinderrance", "optc": "Hindrence", "optd": "Hinderence", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Parallelled", "optb": "Parralleled", "optc": "Paralleled", "optd": "Paraleled", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Lckadaisicle", "optb": "Lackdaisical", "optc": "Lackadisical", "optd": "Lackadaisical", "ans": "D", "explanation": "Lackadaisical - listless, lacking energy, lacking enthusiasm, disinterested, apathetic, lazy"}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Equanimity", "optb": "Equannimity", "optc": "Equanimmity", "optd": "Equinimity", "ans": "A", "explanation": "Equanimity is a calm state of mind and attitude to life, so that you never lose your temper or become upset."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Occured", "optb": "Occurad", "optc": "Ocurred", "optd": "Occurred", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Swelte", "optb": "Filpant", "optc": "Licentious", "optd": "Puessile", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Grief", "optb": "Breif", "optc": "Recieve", "optd": "Diceive", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Furnituer", "optb": "Exampel", "optc": "Medicine", "optd": "Sampal", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Eflorescence", "optb": "Efllorescence", "optc": "Efflorescence", "optd": "Efflorascence", "ans": "C", "explanation": "Efflorescence - flowering, blossoming"}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Exterminatte", "optb": "Inexpliccable", "optc": "Offspring", "optd": "Reffere", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Occasion", "optb": "Occassion", "optc": "Ocasion", "optd": "Ocassion", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "(solve as per the direction given above)", "opta": "Entrepreneur", "optb": "Entrapreneur", "optc": "Entrepraneur", "optd": "Enterprenuer", "ans": "A", "explanation": "Entrepreneur - one who undertakes and assumes the risk of a business enterprise."}]]}